[
    {
        "num": 1,
        "title": "The Liam Dawson Role",
        "question": "Which player won't play a single game?",
        "name": "eng_noplay",
        "answer": [
            "everyone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 2,
        "question": "What will England's run rate be?",
        "title": "500 out of the question?",
        "name": "eng_runrate",
        "answer": [
            "5.51 to 6"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 3,
        "title": "Keep it tight, or not...",
        "question": "Which bowler will have the worst economy rate?",
        "name": "eng_expensiveBowling",
        "answer": [
            "Sam Curran"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 4,
        "title": "Pole-less",
        "question": "Which bowler will take the fewest wickets?",
        "name": "eng_fewestwickets",
        "answer": [
            "Joe Root"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 5,
        "title": "Get on with it",
        "question": "Who will have the lowest batting strike rate?",
        "name": "eng_strikerate",
        "answer": [
            "Liam Livingstone"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 6,
        "title": "No! Down!",
        "question": "Who will drop the most catches?",
        "name": "eng_drops",
        "answer": [
            "Joe Root"
        ]
    },
    {
        "num": 7,
        "title": "Don't Overstep then",
        "question": "What percentage of free hits will go for six?",
        "name": "num_freehits",
        "answer" : 20
    },
    {
        "num": 8,
        "title": "Runs on the board",
        "question": "What will be the average first innings score?",
        "name": "num_firstinns",
        "answer" : 287
    },
    {
        "num": 9,
        "title": "Giant Killers",
        "question": "How many wickets will the Netherlands take?",
        "name": "num_dutchwkts",
        "answer" : 70
    },
    {
        "num": 10,
        "title": "Michael Gough FTW",
        "question": "How many umpires' decisions will be overturned?",
        "name": "num_umpires",
        "answer" : 50
    },
    {
        "num": 11,
        "title": "Sting in the tail",
        "question": "How will be the top score made by a tailender (9-11)?",
        "name": "num_tailenderruns",
        "answer" : 43
    },
    {
        "num": 12,
        "title": "ANOTHER UNACADEMY CRACKING SIX",
        "question": "How many sixes will be hit?",
        "name": "num_totalsixes",
        "answer" : 612
    },
    {
        "num": 13,
        "title": "Oh no, not another one!?",
        "question": "There will be a superover?",
        "name": "h2h_superover",
        "answer" : "false"
    },
    {
        "num": 14,
        "title": "Let it turn",
        "question": "What will take more wickets?",
        "name": "h2h_pacespin",
        "answer" : "pace"
    },
    {
        "num": 15,
        "title": "Win the toss and...",
        "question": "What will teams opt to do more?",
        "name": "h2h_tossDecision",
        "answer" : "bowl first"
    },
    {
        "num": 16,
        "title": "Runs on the board?.",
        "question": "What will win more games?",
        "name": "h2h_bat-v-chase",
        "answer" :["chase total"]
    },
    {
        "num": 17,
        "title": "This is it. The big one.",
        "question": "India or Pakistan or Game Cancelled?",
        "name": "h2h_india_v_pakistan",
        "answer" : "india"
    },
    {
        "num": 18,
        "title": "Bigus Hittus",
        "question": "Pick 2 players. +1 point for each six they hit.",
        "name": "multi_sixes"
    },
    {
        "num": 19,
        "title": "Gun Fielding",
        "question": "Pick 2 players. +10 point for each run out",
        "name": "multi_runouts"
    },
    {
        "num": 20,
        "title": "Howzat!?",
        "question": "Pick 2 players. +1 points for every wicket they take",
        "name": "multi_wickets"
    },
    {
        "num": 21,
        "title": "Top run getters",
        "question": "Pick 2 players. +10pts for 1st, +9pts for 2nd, etc...",
        "name": "multi_mostruns"
    },
    {
        "num": 22,
        "title": "Last WC?",
        "question": "Place the 'Big 4' in order of runs scored. +2 for each correct",
        "name": "multi_bigfour"
    },
    {
        "num": 23,
        "title": "Group Standings",
        "question": "5pts correct, 3pts one out, 1pt two out",
        "name": "standings"
    }
]